ibg.com 2011-11-01

# Privacy Policy

### OUR COMMITMENT TO PRIVACY

Your privacy is very important to us. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used.

### THE TYPES OF PERSONAL INFORMATION COLLECTED ARE AS FOLLOWS:

  * Name
  * Company name (if applicable)
  * Address
  * Email address
  * Phone number
  * Web address (if applicable)

We use this information to provide our services. We do not share your information with any other companies. You will not receive solicitation emails or phone calls from [Info@IBG.com](mailto:Info@IBG.com).

We use return email addresses to answer the email the inquiries we receive. Such addresses are not used for any other purpose and are not shared with outside parties.

We have the highest commitment to data security. To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.

Your privacy is important to us. This Privacy Notice describes the information we collect and how we use that information. Our Privacy Notice is applicable if you have ever submitted personal information to us.

We are committed to protecting your privacy and to implementing technology that gives you a secure online experience. We maintain physical, electronic and procedural safeguards to transmit and store information about you. For instance, we may use computer virus protection software, and firewall's for data transmission. We routinely evaluate security technology and techniques to protect your information.

You may express a preference for receiving telephone and e-mail contacts from us. Specifically, we may send you e-mails or call you regarding our service from time to time. If you do not wish to receive these e-mails or phone calls, you may contact Customer Service by visiting our contact us web page to change your contact preferences. If you elect to opt out of receiving contacts by telephone or e-mail, you will not receive updates on new product information or special offers. 

Notwithstanding the above, we may send periodic e-mails informing you of technical service issues related to a service you requested.

In addition, we reserve the right to contact you regarding changes to this Privacy Notice or any other policies or agreements relevant to your use of this Web site. 

Because circumstances and technologies change, we reserve the right to change this Privacy Notice at any time by notifying you of the existence and location of the new or revised Privacy Notice or by posting the changes online at our Web site.

You also have a significant role in protecting your information. Do not share your personal information with others. If you use this Web site, you are responsible for maintaining the confidentiality of your information. 

To help ensure we are publishing content users need and want we collect aggregated site visitation statistics using cookies. We do not track individuals' use of the Web site. When someone visits the Web site, a cookie is placed on the visitor's machine (if the visitor accepts cookies). If you choose not to have your browser accept cookies from our Web site, you will not be able to subscribe to the service offerings on the Web site.

If you have any questions about this Privacy Notice or the practices of this Web site, please contact us by emailing [Info@Ibg.com](mailto:Info@Ibg.com)
